<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on 🧔 Sanoop&#39;s Space</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on 🧔 Sanoop&#39;s Space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.135.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 05:54:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Part 2 - Home Lab: Extending homenetwork to attic</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/home-lab-journey-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 05:54:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/home-lab-journey-part-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There I was, staring at a tangled mess of Ethernet cables, jacks, and tools, completely clueless about where to start. It was a humbling moment, and honestly, a bit frustrating. What seemed like a straightforward plan to set up a home network from my living room to the attic had quickly turned into a chaotic reality. But it was all part of the process, and I was about to learn way more than I ever imagined — from crimping cables and wiring standards to discovering that routers are often full of surprises.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part 1 - Home Lab: How It All Started and My Initial Network Setup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/home-lab-journey-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 18:43:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/home-lab-journey-part-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For years, I had been toying with the idea of setting up a home lab. As someone who works in tech—programming, managing engineering teams, and designing solutions—getting my hands dirty with technology is second nature to me. But for some reason, starting my home lab was something I kept putting off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;procrastination-and-the-tipping-point&#34;&gt;Procrastination and the Tipping Point&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For months, I kept putting off starting my home lab. Every time I thought about it, the sheer amount of work involved made me pause—running Ethernet cables through the house, purchasing new hardware, and reconfiguring the network all felt overwhelming. With limited spare time outside of work, it was easier to stick with my current setup and tell myself, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll get to that home lab project soon.&amp;rdquo; But, soon kept getting pushed further down the line.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
